http://www.midwaygrinding.com/privacy-policy.html

SERVICESCenterless Grinding
(Infeed/Plunge Grinding)Centerless Grinding (Thru-feed Grinding)Cylindrical OD GrindingI.D. HoningInternal / Bore GrindingPAST PROJECTSPrecision Grinding
of a High Precision Hydraulic PoppetI.D. Honing of Hydraulic SleevesCylindrical & ID Grinding of a Spline Coupling Gear ISO 9001 Certified
Tweet
Print This Page
Email This PagePrivacy PolicyMidway Grinding Inc. respects your privacy and our site visitors' information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.Information Collected
If you request or submit information to us by sending an Email via info@midwaygrinding.com or by filling out a "contact" form, we may save your Email address as well as any other information you provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, Email, or phone to convey information about our solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your Email and other information will not be sold to any third party.Information Collected by Others
This notice addresses only Midway Grinding Inc.'s website policy, and does not apply to sites that users access via links from our site. Midway Grinding Inc. is not responsible for the information collecting policies of other sites, for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, or for the information or content contained therein. Often, links to other websites are provided solely on the basis that they may contain useful information for our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.Cookies
Midway Grinding Inc.'s website does not use cookies.Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information
If you would like to have your personal information removed from our records, please send an Email with "Remove personal information" in the subject line.Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information
Midway Grinding Inc. may disclose information when legally compelled to do so: when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so or for the protection of our legal rights.Periodic Policy Changes
Please note that Midway Grinding Inc. reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.This policy statement is made in the name of Midway Grinding Inc. and is effective as of June 25, 2013. This statement does not create an agreement between Midway Grinding Inc. and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.Contact Us:Midway Grinding Inc.
1451 Lunt Avenue
Elk Grove Village, IL 60007
Tel: 847.439.7424
Fax: 847.439.7459
Email: info@midwaygrinding.com
Web Address: www.midwaygrinding.com
